

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

## **Summary** <sub>-</sub>

Current Computer Science Undergraduate at UNSW. Experience in digital signal processing, quantum computing and natural language processing. Research interests lie in question answering, language model and vision-language grounding. Super nerd who loves Python, C++ and Linux and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

## Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

**Monash Univeristy** Melbourne, Victoria

RESEARCH ASSISTANT, SUPERVISED BY Reza Haffari AND Lizhen Qu

May. 2020 - Present

- Working closely with PhD students in the team on several NLP projects.
- · Proposed a zero-shot question answering model that improves over the state-of-the-art QA models.
- Co-authored a long paper in COLING 2020.

**UNSW Sydney** Sydney, Australia

CASUAL ACADEMIC Feb. 2020 - Present

- Teaching in ENGG1000: Introduction to Engineering Design and Innovation
- Teaching in **ELEC2134: Circuits and Signals**. The only undergraduate in the team while remains are PhDs.

#### Quantum Computation and Communication Technology (CQC2T), UNSW Sydney

Sydney, Australia

RESEARCH STUDENT, SUPERVISED BY Arne Laucht

Nov. 2019 - Sep. 2020

- Proposed a research project of digitizing the lock-in amplifier in MATLAB.
- · Proposed the implementation structure of the digitizing lock-in amplifier in the team's quantum computing system.

Microsoft Shanghai, China

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

Dec. 2019 - Feb. 2020

- Applied Azure SQL DB/DW, Azure Data Lake Storage, Azure Data Lake Analytics, Azure Machine Learning, Stream Analytics, Azure Data Factory, or Cosmos DB to companies' data.
- Designed cloud architecture for top tier companies.
- · Strongly recommended by Michael Wang.

# **Project**

#### Off-world Robotics Project, Vertically Integrated Project

UNSW Sydney

RESEARCHER

Feb. 2020 - Present

- · Determineing the constraints of our embedded systems, sourcing embedded boards for use on the prototype rovers, and testing them with an RTOS or scheduling architecture.
- · Researching existing approaches to the SLAM problem, comparing them, and proposing a SLAM system for use on the rovers.

Py Googletrans Github

CONTRIBUTOR, COLLABORATOR

May. 2020 - Present

May. 2020 - Present

- · Star: 2.0k
- · Fork: 408
- · Googletrans: Free and Unlimited Google translate API for Python. Translates totally free of charge.

#### Sphinx Markdown Builder

Githuh

CONTRIBUTOR

· Star: 79

· Sphinx builder that outputs markdown files.

# Education

NOVEMBER 20, 2020 TERRY ZHUO · RÉSUMÉ

#### **UNSW Sydney (University of New South Wales)**

Sydney, Australia

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING (MINOR IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING)

Jul. 2018 - Sep. 2021(Expected)

• Weighed Average Mark 88.2

# Extracurricular Activity \_\_\_\_\_

**BLUESAT**UNSW Sydney

Power Engineer

- Working on the satellite project which will be launched in 2021-2022.
- Supervising in MPPT board testing and designing.

ELSOC UNSW UNSW Sydney

ACADEMIC TUTOR, SUB-COMMITTEE MEMBER

May. 2019 - Present

Oct. 2019 - Present

• Ran crashcourses (lectures) where more than twenty students on average attended.

## Publication \_\_\_\_\_

# COSMO: Conditional SEQ2SEQ-based Mixture Model for Zero-Shot Commonsense Question Answering

**COLING 2020** 

FARHAD MOGHIMIFAR, LIZHEN QU, YUE ZHUO, MAHSA BAKTASHMOTLAGH AND GHOLAMREZA HAFFARI

### Honors & Awards

2019	Dean's Honours List (Highly Commended), Top 2% of UNSW Engineering	Sydney
2019	Taste of Research scholarships Recipient (A\$5,000), TOP 12 of UNSW Engineering	Sydney
2020	Taste of Research scholarships Recipient (A\$6,000), TOP 43 of UNSW Engineering	Sydney

## Service\_\_\_\_\_

2020	Volunteer, EMNLP 2020	Online
2020	Volunteer, NeurIPS 2020	Online
2020	Volunteer, WiNLP 2020	Seattle, WA

November 20, 2020 Terry Zhuo · Résumé 2